Now we're going to start moving around a little bit in our hoop.
We're going to talk about turning and moving our feet.
Once again, place the hoop on your back and let's give it a whirl.
Get it spinning.
As it's spinning, really notice the hoop pressing into your stomach and your back as Hannah explained.
If you're hooping to your left like we do, as the hoop presses into your left hip, slowly start to turn your body in small circles.
Feel how the hoop just glides and guides you around.
Now, if you turn in the opposite direction, notice how fast the hoop goes.
One, you feel like you're kind of in the middle of a blender.
It's a really interesting, so definitely try turning in the opposite direction.
As you move, you can lift one foot up, lift the other foot up.
You can point a toe moving back and forth.
You can bump your hips back and forth and have a lot of fun with it.
You can also turn pretty quickly coming up on your toes.
You can turn in the other direction a little bit more quickly, keeping it going.
Remember to move around.
Have fun with the hoop.